Guide to the Paul Jeffrey Papers, 1969-2006
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Series V: Oversize Music Manuscripts, (66 boxes)
  - Hamlet's Favorite Son, (2 copies) (Box 164)
  - Hang In There (Box 164)
  - Hank's Other Bag, (2 copies) (Box 164)
  - Heavy Dance (Box 164)
  - Helen's Song, (4 copies) (Box 165)
  - Here Comes That Rainy Day (Box 165)
  - Hi Fly (Box 165)
  - Hiatus (Box 165)
  - Hick's Time, (2 copies) (Box 165)
  - Hip Or Critical? (Box 165)
  - Hot House (Box 165)
  - How Deep Is The Ocean (Box 165)
  - I Can Dream Can't I (Box 166)
  - I Can't Get Started (Box 166)
  - I Got Rhythm (Box 166)
  - I Let A Song Go Out Of My Heart (Box 166)
  - I Mean You, (3 copies) (Box 166)
  - I Thought It Was Understood, (2 copies) (Box 166)
  - Ides Of March, The (Box 166)
  - If I Were A Bell (Box 166)
  - Impressions, (2 copies) (Box 166)
  - In A Mellow Tone, (2 copies) (Box 166)
  - In A Sentimental Mood (Box 166)
  - In Love In L. A., (2 copies) (Box 166)
  - In The Mood (Box 167)
  - In The Vein Of Trane (Box 167)
  - In Vogue, (2 copies) (Box 167)
  - In Walked Bud (Box 167)
  - Inner Visions (Box 167)
  - Intimacy Of The Blues, The (Box 167)
  - Is That So (Box 167)
  - Isms (Box 167)
  - Isn't She Lovely (Box 167)
  - Israel (Box 167)
  - It Ain't Necessarily So (Box 167)
  - It's All Right With Me (Box 167)
  - It's Alright (Box 167)
  - I've Never Been In Love Before, (3 copies) (Box 167)
  - Jackie-ing, (2 copies) (Box 168)
  - Jamba (Box 168)
  - Jazz Corner (Box 168)
  - Jeannie's Waltz (Box 168)
  - Jessica's Day (Box 168)
  - Jitterbug Waltz, (2 copies) (Box 168)
  - Jodo, (2 copies) (Box 168)
  - Joy Spring (Box 169)
  - Juicy Fruit (Box 169)
  - Just The Facts (Box 169)
  - Just The Way You Are (Box 169)
  - Kay Dee (Box 169)
  - Kenny Dorham Medley (Box 169)
  - Kid From The Red Bank, The (Box 169)
  - King David Suite (Box 169)
  - Kiwi Bird (Box 169)
  - Ko-Ko (Box 169)
  - L. A. After Dark (Box 170)
  - La Bossa (Box 170)
  - Lady Barbara (Box 170)
  - Lament, (2 copies) (Box 170)
  - Lament For Booker (Box 170)
  - Landmarks, (2 copies) (Box 170)
  - LaShelle, (2 copies) (Box 170)
  - Last Train From Overbrook (Box 170)
  - Leap Frog (Box 170)
  - Leslie (Box 170)
  - Liber Tad Ahorra (Box 170)
  - Light Blue, (2 copies) (Box 171)
  - Light Within, (3 copies) (Box 171)
  - Like What Is This, (3 copies) (Box 171)
  - Lil' White (Box 171)
  - Little Niles (Box 171)
  - Little Suzie, (2 copies) (Box 171)
  - Little Willie Leaps (Box 171)
  - Long Long Wait, The, (3 copies) (Box 172)
  - Lonley (Box 172)
  - Lo's Step (Box 172)
  - Love To Keep Me Warm (Box 172)
  - Low Tide (Box 172)
  - Lullaby Of Birdland (Box 172)
  - Main Stem (Box 172)
  - Mama Inez (Box 172)
  - Mango Mangue, (3 copies) (Box 172)
  - Maniac (Box 173)
  - Manteca (Box 173)
  - Marmaduke (Box 173)
  - Maybe So (Box 173)
  - Meeting, The (Box 173)
  - Melchizedek, (2 copies) (Box 173)
  - Midnight Sun (Box 173)
  - Miles Ahead (Box 173)
  - Milestones (Box 173)
  - Minister's Son (Box 173)
  - Minor Mishap (Box 174)
  - Minor Sax, A (Box 174)
  - Minor Thesis (Box 174)
  - Mirrors (Box 174)
  - Moment's Notice, (2 copies) (Box 174)
  - Mommy, (2 copies) (Box 174)
  - Monk's Dream, A (Box 174)
  - Monk's Mood, (2 copies) (Box 174)
  - Montmartre (Box 174)
  - Moon Madness (Box 174)
  - Motivation (Box 174)
  - Move (Box 175)
  - Mr. Kenyatta (Box 175)
  - My Flower, (2 copies) (Box 175)
  - My Romance (Box 175)
  - My Ship (Box 175)
  - Naima's Love Song (Box 175)
  - Nardis, (2 copies) (Box 175)
  - Nearness (Box 175)
  - Nearness Of You, The (Box 175)
  - Nelba's Struggle, (2 copies) (Box 175)
  - Niama (Box 175)
  - Niamia (Box 175)
  - Nica's Dream (Box 175)
  - Nice To Come Home To (Box 175)
  - Nickel Whistle (Box 175)
  - Night In Tunisia, A, (2 copies) (Box 176)
  - Nihon Bashi (Box 176)
  - Nioka (Box 176)
  - No Doub't, (4 copies) (Box 176)
  - O Lord We Praise You (Box 176)
  - Oahu Lizard (Box 176)
  - Ode To Vivian, (3 copies) (Box 176)
  - Oh Yeah (Box 176)
  - Old Folks (Box 176)
  - Old King Dooji (Box 176)
  - Oliloqui Valley, (2 copies) (Box 177)
  - On The Edge (Box 177)
  - On The Nile (Box 177)
  - Once Upon A Moon (Box 177)
  - One Bass Hit (Box 177)
  - One By One (Box 177)
  - One For George (Box 177)
  - One For Juan (Box 177)
  - One Man Blues, (3 copies) (Box 177)
  - Opus X (Box 177)
  - Oracle Of The Night (Box 177)
  - Organ Grinder (Box 177)
  - Orient Express (Box 177)
  - Ornithology (Box 177)
  - Oskar T (Box 177)
  - P.G., (3 copies) (Box 178)
  - P.J.'s Delight (Box 178)
  - P.S. I Love You (Box 178)
  - Pannonica (Box 178)
  - Panther (Box 178)
  - Papiro (Box 178)
  - Part Time Love (Box 178)
  - Passageway, (3 copies) (Box 179)
  - Passion Dance (Box 179)
  - Peck A Sec (Box 179)
  - Peggy's Blue Skylight, (3 copies) (Box 179)
  - Perdido, (2 copies) (Box 179)
  - Perhaps (Box 179)
  - Philly-N.Y. Junction, (2 copies) (Box 179)
  - Philly-N.Y. Junction, (2 copies) (Box 180)
  - Picasso (Box 180)
  - Ping Pong (Box 180)
  - Pink Elephant Magic, (2 copies) (Box 180)
  - Played Twice, (2 copies) (Box 180)
  - Plexus, (2 copies) (Box 180)
  - Poinciana (Box 180)
  - Poron Pon Pon (Box 180)
  - Portrait Of Sylvia, (2 copies) (Box 181)
  - Positivity, (2 copies) (Box 181)
  - Presence Of Dr. B, The, (2 copies) (Box 181)
  - Prince Albert (Box 181)
  - Princess Neh Neh, (2 copies) (Box 181)
  - Pursuer, The (Box 181)
  - Queer Notions (Box 181)
  - Quiet Fire, (2 copies) (Box 181)
  - Radius (Box 182)
  - Ray's Idea (Box 182)
  - Re-Affirmation (Box 182)
  - Reed And A Half (Box 182)
  - Reflection, (2 copies) (Box 182)
  - Reincarnation Of A Love Birdm, For Charles Mingus (Box 182)
  - Rejoicin' (Box 182)
  - Rejuvenation (Box 182)
  - Relativity (Box 182)
  - Remember There's Hope, (2 copies) (Box 182)
  - Renee (Box 182)
  - Rhythm-A-Ning (Box 183)
  - Road To Gaza (Box 183)
  - Rockin' In Rhythm (Box 183)
  - Rogi (Box 183)
  - Rosewood, (4 copies) (Box 183)
  - Round Midnight, (2 copies) (Box 184)
  - Runnin' Wild (Box 184)
  - Ruth, (3 copies) (Box 184)
  - Sacrifice, The, (4 copies) (Box 184)
  - Salsa Ein Burgemeister (Box 184)
  - Sao Paulo (Box 184)
  - Satan (Box 184)
  - Satellite, (2 copies) (Box 184)
  - Satin Doll (Box 184)
  - Say It Softly (Box 184)
  - Say Yes To Your Best (Box 185)
  - Scenic Route, The, (4 copies) (Box 185)
  - Scrapple (Box 185)
  - Scratchin' In The Gravel (Box 185)
  - Sea Scape (Box 185)
  - Second Guess (Box 185)
  - Self-Twisting Arm, The (Box 185)
  - Senorita Fife (Box 185)
  - Sentimental Journey (Box 185)
  - Serpent's Tooth, The (Box 185)
  - Settin' Red, (2 copies) (Box 186)
  - Seven Steps To Heaven (Box 186)
  - Sevens, (2 copies) (Box 186)
  - Seventy Seven G Street (Box 186)
  - Shadrach (Box 186)
  - Shawnee (Box 186)
  - Shiny Stockings (Box 186)
  - Shocking News (Box 186)
  - Show Must Go On (Box 186)
  - Sidewinder, The (Box 186)
  - Sid's Delight (Box 186)
  - Siesta (Box 186)
  - Silver's Serenade (Box 186)
  - Six For Kim, (3 copies) (Box 187)
  - Skin Deep (Box 187)
  - Skippy (Box 187)
  - Sky Piece (Box 187)
  - Slow Freight (Box 187)
  - Smile School (Box 187)
  - So What (Box 187)
  - Soft Shoe (Box 187)
  - Someone To Watch Over Me (Box 187)
  - Something You Got Baby (Box 187)
  - Song Is You, The, (2 copies) (Box 188)
  - Song Of Courage (Box 188)
  - Sophisticated Lady (Box 188)
  - SOS (Box 188)
  - Soul Bossa (Box 188)
  - Soulful Sin (Box 188)
  - South Dante, (2 copies) (Box 188)
  - Speak Memory (Box 188)
  - Speak No Evil, (2 copies) (Box 188)
  - Spiral (Box 189)
  - Spoons, (2 copies) (Box 189)
  - St. Louis Blues (Box 189)
  - Stablemates, (2 copies) (Box 189)
  - Stareyes, (2 copies) (Box 189)
  - Stella By Starlight, (2 copies) (Box 189)
  - Stepping Stone (Box 189)
  - Stockholm Sweetening (Box 189)
  - Stompin' At The Savoy (Box 189)
  - Stormy Monday (Box 189)
  - Straight No Chaser, (2 copies) (Box 189)
  - Strike Up The Band (Box 190)
  - Subliminal Seduction, (2 copies) (Box 190)
  - Suite Newport In New York (Box 190)
  - Summer Waltz (Box 190)
  - Sunshine Of My Life (Box 190)
  - Super "80" (Box 190)
  - Susan's Waltz (Box 190)
  - Sweet Georgia Brown (Box 190)
  - Sweet Love Of Mine (Box 190)
  - Swing Thing (Box 190)
  - Synergy, (2 copies) (Box 190)
  - T.B.A. (Box 190)
  - Take Five (Box 190)
  - Tap Dancer, The, (2 copies) (Box 190)
  - Tea For Two (Box 190)
  - Testification, (3 copies) (Box 191)
  - Testimonial, (3 copies) (Box 191)
  - Thabo (Box 191)
  - Thank You (Box 191)
  - That's What Friends Are For (Box 191)
  - Theme, The (Box 191)
  - Theme For Maxine (Box 191)
  - Theme For Penny, (3 copies) (Box 191)
  - Theme Two (Box 191)
  - Things To Come (Box 191)
  - Things Will Never Be The Same (Box 192)
  - Third Day, The (Box 192)
  - This Is For Albert (Box 192)
  - Three And Me (Box 192)
  - Three Shades Of Blue, (3 copies) (Box 192)
  - Thumb, The (Box 192)
  - Tickle Toe (Box 192)
  - Tight (Box 192)
  - Time To Go, (3 copies) (Box 192)
  - Time's Mirror, (2 copies) (Box 193)
  - Timothy (Box 193)
  - Tones For Joan's Bones (Box 193)
  - Too Deep For The Ocean (Box 193)
  - Tragic Magic (Box 193)
  - Trane Connections (Box 193)
  - Trials Of Trust And Treachery, The (Box 193)
  - Troica (Box 193)
  - True Friends, (3 copies) (Box 193)
  - Turnpike, (2 copies) (Box 194)
  - Tu-Way-Pock-E-Way (Box 194)
  - Twelve (Box 194)
  - Twilight Town (Box 194)
  - Ugly Beauty (Box 194)
  - Un Poco Loco (Box 194)
  - Una Mass (Box 194)
  - Unbroken Line (Box 194)
  - Uncle Harvey (Box 194)
  - Up Close And Personal, (2 copies) (Box 194)
  - Urban Omen (Box 194)
  - Valery's Changes (Box 195)
  - Valse Robin (Box 195)
  - Vicious Cycle, The (Box 195)
  - Vines, (3 copies) (Box 195)
  - Vision, The (Box 195)
  - Voices Of Jazz (Box 195)
  - Voodoo Lady, (2 copies) (Box 196)
  - Wail (Box 196)
  - Wake Up Call (Box 196)
  - Walkin' (Box 196)
  - Waltz For Aunt Marie, (2 copies) (Box 196)
  - Waltz For Debby, (2 copies) (Box 196)
  - Waltz For Ima (Box 196)
  - Waltz For Zweetie (Box 197)
  - Waltz Little (Box 197)
  - Waltz You Swang For Me, The (Box 197)
  - Warm Valley (Box 197)
  - We'll Be Together Again, (2 copies) (Box 197)
  - What Am I Here For (Box 197)
  - What Is This Thing Called Love, (3 copies) (Box 197)
  - When I Fall In Love, (3 copies) (Box 197)
  - Whirling, (2 copies) (Box 197)
  - Whirlwind (Box 197)
  - Willie B. (Box 197)
  - Windstar (Box 197)
  - Witchcraft (Box 197)
  - With Love (Box 197)
  - With One More Look At Love (Box 198)
  - Without A Song (Box 198)
  - Woody 1 - On The New Ark (Box 198)
  - Woodyn' You (Box 198)
  - Work (Box 198)
  - Work Song, (2 copies) (Box 198)
  - Worlds Apart, (2 copies) (Box 198)
  - Yeah Man (Box 198)
  - Yes And No (Box 198)
  - You And The Night And The Music, (2 copies) (Box 198)
  - You And The Night And The Music (Box 199)
  - You're Nobody (Box 199)
  - Zodiac Suite: 1. Aries (Box 199)
  - Zodiac Suite: 2. Taurus, (2 copies) (Box 199)
  - Zodiac Suite: 3. Gemini (Box 199)
  - Zodiac Suite: 4. Cancer (Box 199)
  - Zodiac Suite: 5. Leo (Box 199)
  - Zodiac Suite: 6. Virgo (Box 199)
  - Zodiac Suite: 7. Libra (Box 199)
  - Zodiac Suite: 8. Scorpio (Box 199)
  - Zodiac Suite: 10. Capricorn (Box 199)
  - Zodiac Suite: 11. Aquarius (Box 199)
  - Zodiac Suite: 12. Pisces (Box 199)
  - Unidentified scores and fragments (Box 200)
  - Unidentified scores and fragments (Box 201)
  - Unidentified scores and fragments (Box 202)
  - Unidentified scores and fragments (Box 203)
  - Unidentified scores and fragments (Box 204)
  - Unidentified scores and fragments (Box 205)
  - Unidentified scores and fragments (Box 206)